Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode. Subtitles will likely not function properly. Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv: https://mpv.io
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode. Subtitles will likely not function properly. Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv: https://mpv.io
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode. Subtitles will likely not function properly. Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv: https://mpv.io
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode. Subtitles will likely not function properly. Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv: https://mpv.io
Whoa...
Müthiş...
Alright!
Tamam!
Aw, not again...
Aman, yine mi...
Batter out!
Vurucu dışarı!
What're you doing?
Ne yapıyorsun?
You suck!
Beceriksiz!
This thing's heavy!
Gerçekten ağır...
Must be filled with booze, then!
O zaman içkiyle dolu olmalı!
Ship off the starboard quarter!
Sancak tarafında tehlike!
It's flying a Jolly Roger!
Direğin tepesinde korsan bayrağı asılı!
It's a pirate ship! Enemy raid! Enemy raid!
Korsan gemisi! Düşman saldırısı! Düşman saldırısı!
Koby!
Koby!
Y-Yes, ma'am?!
E-evet, madam?!
On these seas, who's the fairest of them all?
Bu okyanustaki en güzel kadın kim?
Th-That'd obviously be the captain of this ship, Lady Alvida!
Tabii ki bu geminin kaptanı, Alvida-sama.
You got that right!
İyi dedin!
Th-Thank you so much!
Ç-Çok teşekkür ederim!
Lady Alvida. Been awhile since our last prey.
Alvida-sama, uzun zaman oldu değil mi?
It has.
Doğru!
Alright! Start pounding that ship!
Şimdi gemiyi bordaya alın!
– Yeah!
– Emredersiniz!
Men! Show them the terror of the lady pirate, Iron Club Alvida!
Adamlarım! Onlara demir topuzlu dişi korsan Alvida'nın gücünü gösterin!
Koby! What are you doing?!
Koby! Sen ne yapıyorsun?
I-I'm not good at this sort of thing.
B-Ben bu tür şeylerde pek iyi değilim.
Wha...?!
Ne...?!
Are you talking back to me?!
Bana karşı konuşmaya mı cüret ediyorsun?
P-Please, anything but the club!
Lütfen, demir topuz harici bir şey olsun!
Then get your rear in gear!
Öyleyse çabuk ol ve işe koyul!
We won't take your lives, but we will take all your valuables!
Sizi öldürmeyeceğiz, ama değerli olan her şeyinizi alacağız.
Try to fight back, and you'll just end up at the bottom of the ocean!
Direniş gösteren herkes okyanusa atılacak!
Hello...?
Merhaba...?
No one's in here, right?
Burada kimse yok, değil mi...?
Thank goodness... Hm?
Tanrı'ya şükür... Hm?
What a big barrel...
Bu oldukça büyük bir fıçı.
Hey, wimp!
Hey, korkak!
Hiding out again to skip out on duties, huh?!
Yine saklanıp hiçbir şey yapmadan duruyor musun?
N-No! I thought I should just roll this barrel of booze over...
Hiç de değil! Bu şarap fıçısını ittiriyordum...
Allow us to lighten the load!
Yükünü hafifletmemize izin ver!
I was just getting thirsty...
Çok susadık.
You can't! Lady Alvida will kill us if she finds out!
Olamaz! Eğer Alvida-sama bunu öğrenirse, öldürülürsünüz.
Then you just gotta keep your mouth shut!
Eğer çeneni kapalı tutarsan bir şey olmaz.
Right, Koby?
Değil mi, Koby?
Y-Yes! Absolutely!
E-Evet! Kesinlikle!
It's damn heavy...
Oldukça ağır...
I can't wait!
Sabırsızlanıyorum!
I'll bust it right open!
Hemen açacağım!
What a great nap!
NE HARİKA BİR ŞEKERLEMEEEEEEE!
Huh?
Ne?
Who are you guys?
Siz de kimsiniz?
– Who the hell are you?!
– Asıl sen kimsin lan?!
He'll catch a cold napping there.
Eğer burda uyursa üşütecek.
– Because of you!
– Bu senin hatan!
Bastard...! Who do you think you are, messing with pirates, huh?!
Pislik...!
Man, I'm hungry! You got any food?
Acıktım! Yiyecek bir şeyin var mı?
Don't just ignore us!
Bizi görmezden gelme!
You damn brat!
Seni lanet velet!
Die!
Geber!
What's the big idea?
Böyle aniden ne yapıyorsunuz?
Wh-Who are you?!
K... Kimsin sen?
Me?
Ben mi?
I'm Monkey D. Luffy. Nice to meet you!
Ben, Monkey D. Luffy. Memnun oldum!
What the...? What just happened?
Demin... demin ne oldu öyle?
What's with them?
Onların sorunu ne?
H-Hurry! Get out of here!
Çabuk! Hemen kaç!
If they come back with their friends, you'll be killed!
Arkadaşlarıyla birlikte geri geldikleri zaman, seni öldürecekler!
But man, I sure am hungry!
Öyle bile olsa, çok açım!
How can you be so carefree?!
Nasıl bu kadar pervasız olabiliyorsun?!
There are still lots more of them up on deck!
Güvertede bir sürü korsan var!
C'mon! This way!
O tarafa gitme.
H-H-Hey!
D-D-Dur!
Not this way!
Yanlış yöne gidiyorsun!
Food! Food! Food! Yes! Food!
Yiyecek! Yiyecek! Yiyecek! Yaşasın!
Actually, they might not find us in here!
Aslında bizi burada bulamayabilirler!
Which should I choose? This box? Oh, jackpot!
Hangisini alsam acaba? Bu kutuyu mu? Oh, bingo.
These look tasty!
Çok lezzetli görünüyorlar!
M-My name is Koby.
B-Benim adım Koby.
You're Luffy, right?
Sen Luffy-san'sın, değil mi?
That was incredible just now! How did you do that?!
Az önce inanılmazdın! Bunu nasıl yaptın?!
These things are great!
Bunlar harika!
Is this a pirate ship?
Bu gemi, korsan gemisi mi?
No, it's a passenger ship that's being plundered by Lady Alvida.
Hayır, bu gemi, Alvida-sama tarafından yağmalanan bir yolcu gemisi.
Makes no difference to me.
Benim için farketmez.
Are there any small boats on board?
Bu gemide hiç sandal var mı?
I-I think so...
Olabilir, ama...
My boat got swallowed by this giant whirlpool!
Benim gemim girdaba yakalandı.
You mean that whirlpool?! It's a wonder you survived!
Eh, o girdaba mı? Ölmüş olmalıydın.
Boy, was that a real surprise!
Evet, beni gerçekten endişelendirdi.
Are you a pirate like them, or what?
Sen de onlar gibi korsan mısın?
Hm?
Hm?
It was on that fateful day...
O gün... vahim bir gündü.
That day, I got in a boat on the outskirts of town to go fishing...
O gün, balığa çıkmak niyetiyle sandala binmiştim...
but it turned out the boat was actually headed for a pirate ship.
Ama o sandal korsan gemisine doğru gidiyordu!
It's been two years now.
Geçtiğimiz 2 yıldan beri,...
In exchange for my life, I was forced to work as a cabin boy.
...beni öldürmemeleri için köle gibi çalışıyorum.
Man, you're a real idiot!
Gerçekten aptalsın!
You're brutally honest.
Son derece dürüstsün.
Then just run away!
Kaçabilirsin!
I-I can't! No way! No way!
Y-Yapamam! İmkansız, imkansız!
The thought of Lady Alvida finding me makes me weak in the knees.
Alvida-sama'nın beni bulması düşüncesi bile dizlerimi titretiyor.
Oh, you're a wimp too?
Ne, sen şu korkak olanlardan mısın?
I really can't stand you!
Senden hoşlanmadım.
Hey, now! Quit slacking off!
Hey, gevşemeyi bırakın da acele edin.
Haul it all over before the Marines get here!
Denizciler buraya gelmeden her şeyi taşıyın!
Any dawdlers get a taste of my iron club!
Her kim işi gevşek tutarsa, demir topuzumun tadına bakar!
What a haul!
Ne ganimet ama!
– Lady Alvida!
– Alvida-sama!
– Bad news!
– Sorun var!
What is it?! You're ticking me off!
Ne oldu? Çok gürültü yapıyorsunuz.
A b-b-barrel!
F-f-fıçı!
I-It's a monster!
Y-Yaratık!
Huh?!
Ha?!
Who are you calling a "monster"?!
Kimmiş yaratık?
N-No...
Yanlış anladınız...
Some weird guy popped out of a barrel...
Fıçıdan garip bir adam çıktı...
He might be a bounty hunter...
Ödül avcısı olabilir.
What?!
Ne?!
Yeah.
Evet.
That's right.
Haklısın.
If only I had your courage to drift the seas in a barrel...
Keşke bir varilin içinde denizlerde savrulacak kadar cesaretim olsaydı,...
then I'd be able to accomplish what I really want, too.
...o zaman gerçekten istediğim şeyi başarmış olurdum.
Um... What compelled you to set out to sea, Luffy?
Şey... Seni denize açılmaya ne itti, Luffy-san?
Huh?
Ha?
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
Ben, Korsanlar Kralı olacağım!
K-K-King of the Pirates?!
Ko-Ko-Korsanlar Kralı mı?!
Yep.
Aynen.
Are you serious?!
Ciddi misin?!
I'm serious.
Ciddiyim.
Wait, you're a pirate, Luffy?!
Yani Luffy-san, sende mi korsansın?
Yep.
Tabii.
And your crew...?
Peki tayfan...?
Don't have one. I'm looking, though.
Hiç yok, ama şu anda bulmaya çalışıyorum.
Th-Th-The King of the Pirates is the person who obtains everything this world has to offer!
K-K-Korsanlar Kralı, bu dünyanın sunduğu her şeyi elde eden kişidir!
That means seeking ultimate wealth, fame, and power—
Bu, en büyük zenginliği, şöhreti ve gücü aramak anlamına gelir.
the One Piece, the greatest hidden treasure!
One Piece'in peşinden gittiğini söyleme bana.
Yup!
Aynen!
"Yup"?! Pirates all over the world are after that treasure!
"Aynen mi"?! Dünyadaki bütün korsanlar o hazinenin peşinden gidiyor!
Me too!
Ben de gidiyorum!
No way! No way, no way, no way! Absolutely no way!
İmkansız, imkansız, imkansız, imkansız, kesinlikle imkansız!
There's no way you can stand at the summit of this Great Pirate Era!
Bu Büyük Korsan Çağı'nın zirvesine çıkman imkansız!
No way! No way!
İmkansız! İmkansız!
Why'd you hit me?
Bana niye vurdun?
I felt like it.
İçimden geldi.
I guess it's fine... I'm used to it now.
Sorun değil, nasıl olsa buna alıştım.
It's not about whether I can...
İmkansız olup olmaması önemli değil.
Huh?
Ha?
I'll do it because I wanna.
Bunu istediğim için yapıyorum.
I've decided to become King of the Pirates...
Ben, Korsanlar Kralı olmaya karar verdim.
so if I die fighting for that, then fine by me!
Bu yolda ölsem bile farketmez.
Well, I'm stuffed! Guess I'll go find a boat.
Artık doyduğuma göre, gidip bir sandal alabilirim.
I wonder if they'll give me one.
Acaba bana bir tane verirler mi?
I hope they're generous.
Umarım cömert olurlar.
The thought never even crossed my mind...
Bunu hiç düşünmemiştim.
Do you think I could do it too...
Bunu ben de yapabilir miyim?
if I'm prepared to die for it?
Ölmekten korkmadan.
Do what?
Neyi?
Do you think...
Sence...
I could join the Marines?
...donanmaya katılabilir miyim?
The Marines?
Donanma mı?!
Yes! Catching bad guys is my dream!
Evet! Kötü adamları yakalamak benim hayalim!
It's been my dream ever since I was little!
Çocukluğumdan beri hayalimdi!
Do you think I can do it?!
Bunu yapabilir miyim?
How should I know?
Ben nereden bileyim?
No! I'll do it!
Hayır, bunu yapacağım!
I either remain a chore boy or break free and catch Lady Alvida!
Ya hayatım boyunca miço olarak kalırım ya da Alvida-sama'yı...
No, just Alvida!
Hayır, Alvida'yı yakalayıp özgür olurum!
You wanna join up with this punk?!
Böyle arkadaş edinerek...
To catch who exactly?!
...kimi yakalayacaksın?
Huh, Koby?!
Ha, Koby?!
You don't look like Pirate Hunter Zoro.
Korsan Avcısı Zoro'ya hiç benzemiyorsun.
Zoro?
Zoro mu?
Koby!
Koby!
On these seas, who's the fairest of them all?!
Bu okyanusta en güzel kadın kim?!
O-Of course that would be–
E-Elbette siz–
Who's this burly old lady?
Bu şişman kadın kim?
"Burly"?
"Şişman" mı?
He didn't...
Sıçtı...
You runt!
Seni bücür!
Let's go!
Gidelim!
Why, you...!
Seni...!
It's not fair to attack from behind!
Arkadan saldırmak hiç adil değil!
It's also not fair to gang up on people!
Çok fazla kişiyle saldırmak da adil değil!
Gotcha!
Kandırdım!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Rocket!
Roket!
What?!
Nee?!
L-Luffy... What are you?
Luffy-san, nesin sen?
Me?
Ben mi?
I'm a rubber man!
Ben lastik adamım.
A rubber man...? You can't be serious!
Lastik adam mı? Ciddi olamazsın!
You ate a devil fruit, didn't you?
Şeytan meyvesini yedin, değil mi?
Yeah! The Gum-Gum Fruit!
Evet! Lastik-Lastik meyvesini yedim.
I see!
Anlıyorum!
I'd heard the rumors, but I guess they really do exist!
Söylentiler duymuştum ama sanırım gerçekten varlarmış!
You're not too shabby, either.
Sen de fena değilsin.
You a bounty hunter?
Ödül avcısı mısın?
I'm a pirate!
Hayır, korsanım!
A pirate?! Ha!
Korsan mı?! Ha!
All by yourself?!
Tek başına mı?!
It's just me right now, but I'm putting together a crew!
Şu an sadece ben varım ama bir tayfa kuracağım!
I'm thinking... ten people sounds good!
Şöyle bi'... on kişi iyi olur gibi!
Then that means you and me are enemies, huh?
Bu bizi düşman yapıyor, değil mi?
L-Luffy! Let's get out of here!
Lu... Luffy-san, kaç.
Why?
Neden?
You saw how powerful her club is!
O demir topuzun gücünü gördün.
On these seas, she's the number one...
Bu kadın bir numaralı...
I've decided to become King of the Pirates...
Ben, Korsanlar Kralı olmaya karar verdim.
so if I die fighting for that, then fine by me!
Bu yolda ölsem bile farketmez.
I'm the number one... what exactly?
Bir numaralı ne?
Th-Th-The...
Bir... bir... bir...
The number one ugliest, meanest old hag ever!
Bir numaralı kokuşmuş, çirkin ve yaşlı bir kocakarıdır!
Wh-What did you say?!
N-Ne dedin sen?!
I-I'm gonna join the Marines!
B-Ben donanmaya katılacağım!
And then I'll give you pirates hell!
Katılıp senin gibi korsanlarla dövüşeceğim!
Do you even know what you're saying?!
Sen ne dediğinin farkında mısın?!
I do! I'm gonna do what I wanna do!
Farkındayım! Ben istediğim şeyi yapacağım!
When I'm... When I'm a Marine...
Ben... Ben bir denizci olduğumda...
I'm gonna put you away for good!
Seni sonsuza kadar hapse tıkacağım!
You damn pipsqueak!
Seni lanet tıfıl!
No regrets! No regrets! I said it! I fought for my dream!
Pişmanlık yok! Pişmanlık yok! Söyledim! Hayalim için savaştım!
Well said!
İyi dedin!
That won't work!
İşe yaramaz!
What?!
Ne?!
I'm rubber, after all.
Çünkü ben lastiğim.
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Pistol!
Tabanca!
The sky is so blue...
Gökyüzü masmavi...
Hey!
Hey!
– Yes?!
– Evet?!
Give Koby a small boat!
Koby'ye sandal verin.
He's gonna join the Marines!
Donanmaya katılacak.
So just let him go quietly.
Bırakın gitsin.
– R-Right!
– T-Tabii!
Luffy...!
Luffy-san...!
It's the Marines!
Bunlar... Denizciler!
Oh!
Oh!
Perfect timing! You should go see them!
Harika zamanlama! Onları görmelisin!
Huh?
Ha?
But pirates have gotta run!
Ben korsanım, kaçma zamanı!
Seriously?!
Ciddi misin?!
Trying to join the Marines right now will get me captured instead!
Donanmaya böyle katılamam. Giremeden beni tutuklarlar!
We managed to get away, huh?
Neyse ki kaçabildik, ha?
Whew, that was fun!
Uf, çok eğlenceliydi!
Um, Luffy....
Şey, Luffy-san.
Yeah?
Evet?
If you're looking for the One Piece, then you're off to the Grand Line, right?
Eğer One Piece'i arıyorsan, o zaman Grand Line'a gidiyorsun, değil mi?
Yup.
Aynen.
That place is also called the Pirate Graveyard, you know.
O yer aynı zamanda Korsan Mezarlığı olarak da bilinir.
Yeah. So I'll need a strong crew.
Evet, işte bu yüzden güçlü bir tayfaya ihtiyacım var.
What about that Pirate Hunter guy?
Şu korsan avcısı...
What's he like?
O nasıl biri?
You mean Zoro?
Zoro'yu mu kastediyorsun?
I heard he's being held prisoner at a Marine base.
Donanma tarafından yakalandığını duydum.
Oh? He's a weakling?
Ne? O güçsüz biri mi?
Not even!
Hiç de değil!
He's like a terrifying demon!
O dehşet verici bir şeytan!
Why are you asking about him?
Niye bana bunu soruyorsun?
If he's a good guy, I thought he could join my crew!
Eğer iyi biriyse, tayfama alabilirim!
You're being reckless again!
Yine pervasızca bir şey yapacaksın.
C'mon, he might be a good guy!
İyi bir adam olabilir!
He was caught because he's a bad guy!
O kötü bir adam olduğu için yakalandı!
No! No way, no way, no way! Absolutely no–
Hayır! İmkansız, imkansız, imkansız, Kesinlikle imkan–
Why'd you hit me?
Bana niye vurdun?
I felt like it.
İçimden geldi.
Koby A Cabin Boy
"Kamarot" Koby
"Iron Club" Alvida The Lady Pirate
"Demir Topuz" Alvida Kadın Korsan